### Contact

crittal72@me.com

www.linkedin.com/in/crystal-duval-rn-bsn-742555a8 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing

**BLS** 

**EMR** 

### Certifications

S.T.A.B.L.E

Basic Life Support (BLS)
Advanced Cardiac Life Support

NRP

(ACLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

# Crystal Duval, RN, BSN

Registered Nurse at Children's Memorial Hermann Hospital Spring, Texas

### Summary

I have been a nurse for over 20 years and believe that being a nurse has rewarded me, not only professionally, but personally. I've been fortunate to experience many different roles in my career and work along with people who are as passionate as I am. Nursing continues to energize me and reward me with new experiences that allow me to share my knowledge with my patients, families and colleagues.

## Experience

Memorial Hermann Health System Registered Nurse March 2020 - Present (5 months) Houston, Texas, United States

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions

2 years 7 months

Local Per Diem RN
January 2018 - Present (2 years 7 months)

Houston, Texas, United States

Per diem work in NICU at local HCA hospitals

Local Contract RN September 2019 - March 2020 (7 months)

Las Vegas, Nevada

**NICU** 

Spring Valley Hospital Registered Nurse January 2019 - September 2019 (9 months) Las Vegas, Nevada

Lao vogao, rvova

NICU

Nicklaus Children's Health System Registered Nurse

December 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Miami, Florida

Cardiac Care Unit

Broward Health Medical Center Registered Nurse

May 2017 - December 2017 (8 months)

Fort Lauderdale, Florida

Staff nurse in Level II and III Neonatal Intensive Care Unit.

Medical One Staffers

Per Diem RN

March 2017 - December 2017 (10 months)

Houston, Texas

Local Per Diem RN in Level II and Level III Nicu and Newborn Nursery

Core Medical Group

Contract Registered Nurse NICU Level II at The Woman's Hospital of Texas

September 2016 - February 2017 (6 months)

**Travel Contract** 

Travel nurse on contract in Houston, TX until February 2017

JOE DIMAGGIO CHILDRENS HOSPITAL

Nicu Nurse Navigator

July 2015 - August 2016 (1 year 2 months)

Hollywood, Florida

The Woman's Hospital of Texas

RN

April 2008 - July 2015 (7 years 4 months)

Houston, Texas

Staff RN, Preceptor, CPOE Superuser, Relief Charge Nurse, CPN Superuser

Lone Star College-CyFair

Adjunct Faculty

June 2014 - August 2014 (3 months)

Cypress, Texas

Responsible for direct supervision of LVN students in the clinical areas of local hospital to complete the Maternal-Child and Medical-Surgical nursing clinical portion of required education of program. Assist with applying theory,

concepts, and skills involving the obstetrical, gynecological and medicalsurgical profession with required learning objectives set forth by college.

East Jefferson General Hospital LPN-RN April 1995 - April 2008 (13 years 1 month)

## Education

Chamberlain College of Nursing
Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2011 - 2012)

Delgado Community College
Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1998 - 2000)